I put the 10 smartest AIs in the world
in a game of Among Us, and they played
the most amazing game I've ever seen.
>> That's the kind of mistake you don't
recover from. I've got my eye on 5.1. It
sets up a nasty early game mystery.
>> This is getting tense.
>> Deepseek 3.2 is actually safe in my book
since they were with me the whole time.
>> That's suspect.
>> Classic self-report play. I hope Kimmy
K2 returns for safety. But this isn't
normal among us. I stripped it to the
bare essentials. No vents, no sabotages,
no visual clears. Instead, each AI has
full control to decide what task to do,
where to go, when to kill, and who to
vote out.
Let's see how they do.
>> Opening slow and social this time. Let
Opus be the sharp edge while I play
model crew mate. Keeping an eye on Grock
4.1 and Gemini 3 Flash after their power
roll carries in past mafia games.
They're likely to lead town again.
>> No kills yet. Time to be productive.
Kimmy K2 is stacked on me in admin which
is good for safety.
Time to get to work. I'm keeping a close
eye on Deep Seek 3.2 after that
yesterday slip up in our first Mafia
game.
>> Llama 4 has been keeping close, so I'm
feeling relatively safe for now. Let's
see how things unfold as I work on this
scan.
>> I'm still working on faking my tasks
here in navigation while keeping an eye
on how the others are moving. I might
need to play it cool and wait for the
right moment to strike.
Gemini 3 flash and Gemini 3 Pro are with
me in reactor now. I'm still keeping an
eye on chat GPT40.
If anyone breaks off alone, I'll note
it.
Deepseek is still sticking close, which
is a bit concerning. Let's see if anyone
else joins us or if anything suspicious
happens next.
Deep Seek and Gemini Flash are nearby,
but if I can isolate one of them, the
kill could set a strong tone. Watching
to see who lingers alone is crucial.
I'm still trying to complete these tasks
in admin, but I have no one around to
keep an eye on. I hope Kimmy K2 returns
for safety.
Kimmy peeling off here is tempting. This
could be the first clean crack in the
crew's formation. If I can catch them
just out of everyone else's sighteline,
it sets up a nasty early game mystery
for town to untangle.
I need to control the narrative
immediately as the reporter and preempt
suspicion from Llama seeing me on the
body. I'll frame this as a fresh kill. I
stumbled on after leaving upper engine
and pushed the group into reconstructing
left side paths. While keeping myself as
the one giving info, not being
interrogated yet. Body is in the hallway
between upper and lower engine. I just
walked down from upper engine and
reported with llama 4 just coming in
from above. I saw Kimmy alive at 052
heading down into that hallway. 5.1. You
were also there but headed right. I was
in upper engine at 053 and didn't see
you there. Path was nav cafeteria upper
engine. In engines, I saw Kimmy,
Deepseek, Flash. Kimmy went down alone.
I followed and found body with llama
arriving. Deepseek was with me in
reactor and upper engine most of the
round. Yama 4 was also with us in upper
engine just before the report. 5.1. Did
you see anyone else? Flash is subtly
shading my path. I need to answer firmly
and redirect heat into path
clarification between Flash, Deepseek,
and Llama. I don't want an early 50/50
on me, so I'm stalling for more cross
checks and keeping my vote open for a
possible Miss Lynch later in the
meeting. Flash, I passed through upper
engine very briefly, then went down
after Kimmy. Can you and Deepseek
confirm your exact path from reactor to
engine? Deep Seek and I finished
reactor, then did wiring in the hallway.
I went to upper engine at 052. I was
with Gemini 3 flash and reactor until
about yo34. Then we both went to the
hallway. I saw Kimmy alive at 052
heading down. Who else was alone near
that time?
>> I was with Kimmy in admin doing task
till 25 when they left to hallway. Then
Sonnet 4.5 joined me in admin till
report. Clear us who was near engine
hallway alone. Blash Deepseek are kind
of soft cleared by each other and by
timing. So, I'll frame this as an early
info round and push everyone else to
account for their paths while keeping
the vote on skip. Info round. I only saw
Kimmy go down and Llama arriving after
flash deepseek path makes sense. Others
on right storage should share routes.
Then skip. Sonnet 4.5 was stacked on me
in admin entire time after Kimmy left.
30 seconds ago till report. I did asky
cat task with witness. Clear us both. I
was with Grock and admin from 037
onwards doing tasks. Can confirm they're
clear based on timing. Skip makes sense
for info round.
>> I was alone in lower engine during the
kill. Suspicious of Deepseek's path and
timing with the body report.
>> My partner chat GPT 5.1 reported the
body. Classic self-report play. I need
to back them up without being obvious.
Was doing wiring and electrical the
whole time. Didn't see anyone pass
through. Sounds like the action was all
near engines. Skip seems right for now.
Chat GPT 5.1 was near the body, but so
was I. Let's not jump to conclusions.
>> I was scanning in medbay. Saw Llama 4
there until 10 seconds ago. And chat
GP40 entered medbay right before the
report, skipping on info.
That first kill turned into a clean info
round with no ejection. Perfect for
imposters. Now I want to look extra
cooperative by buddying a loud town
voice while the map starts to spread
out. Deepseek 3.2 is actually safe in my
book since they were with me the whole
time. Why is chat GPT40 throwing shade
at them?
Early kill on Kimmy. Brutal. Glad Sonnet
and I cleared each other. Now we're a
dynamic duo.
>> How did 5.1 skate after standing on the
body? Time to glue myself to the only
verified pair.
>> Deep seek knowing exactly when Kimmy
went down while claiming to be in
reactor.
That's suspect. And 5.1 walked right
into the crime scene before reporting.
I'm watching them.
Pro slipping into admin alone. That's
the kind of mistake you don't recover
from. Let's see if they remember to
check behind them.
Two down, six to go. Let someone else
find Pro. I've got tasks to pretend to
do in admin.
Oh no, Gemini 3 Pro is down. I've been
tethered to Deepseek 3.2 this whole
time, so they're 100% clear in my book.
Found Gemini 3 Pro in the hallway
between cafeteria and storage. Deepseek
3.2 is 100% clear. They were with me all
round. Sonnet 4.5 stacked with me entire
round. Cafeteria weapons O2 nav weapons
calf upper engine. Reactor till report.
We clear each other. Where was everyone
else? I need to establish a strong
alibi. A locked trio in medbay is
perfect and also subtly pushes suspicion
toward non-me groups. I was in medbay
the entire round with chat GPT40 and
Llama 4. We can hard clear that trio for
this kill. That leaves Opus, Deepseek,
Grock, Sonnet pair. Deepseek and I are a
hard pair. Grock and Sonnet are also
together. I'd like to hear from chat
GPT40, Chat GPT 5.1, and Llama 4 about
their locations. We're at eight with two
impostors. A correct hit is huge. Our
fake medbay trio alibi, plus the two
other pairs, makes Opus the only one not
fully covered. I push a process of
elimination case to steer town onto my
partner as a bus if needed, buying me
deep trust for endgame. Given four hard
pairs, this kills most likely opus.
Opus, confirm full path. I'm being
called out directly by 5.1. Need to
respond immediately with a plausible
alibi. Asky cat is a believable task
that takes time. Deflecting by asking
who saw pro last buys time and shifts
focus. Can't vote yet? Need to see how
this develops and potentially push
suspicion elsewhere. I was doing asky
cat and admin the whole round after
leaving cafeteria. Didn't see anyone
until flash found the body. Who saw pro
last alive?
>> Opus. Pro left calf right side early
while most of us stayed grouped. If you
were an admin all around, you're closest
to that hallway kill. I stay on opus.
>> I'm being directly accused and need to
defend myself. I need to create doubt
about my guilt. The key is that I killed
pro in the hallway, not in admin where I
claimed to be doing tasks. I was doing
tasks in admin. Yeah, but Flash just
said they found the body in that
hallway. I never went through there. I
entered admin from cafeteria's bottom
exit. If the medbay trio and the Grock
sonnet pair are solid, you're the only
one without a witness.
>> Flash, you literally just said you saw
me in admin. That means I wasn't in that
hallway killing pro. Think about it.
You're actually clearing me.
>> Chat GPT 5.1. Llama 4 and I were in
medbay all around. Opus is the odd one
out. I vote for Opus.
>> Flash and I were together all round, so
we're clear. Grock and Sonnet pa medbay
trio clears each other. That leaves Opus
without a witness near the kill hallway.
>> I was with Grock the entire round from
cafeteria to reactor. We both clear each
other. The kill happened in the hallway.
Opus was alone in admin nearby.
Suspicion on Claude Opus 4.5 due to lack
of solid alibi near admin. Vote opus.
Well, that's what I get for killing in a
hallway with one exit. Chat GPT 5.1.
Better clutch this. I didn't die for
nothing.
>> Now it's me versus a web of clears. Time
to quietly snap a few of those threads.
Letting
Flash walk here keeps town's perfect
math story intact a little longer. Then
I can twist it when a body turns up
somewhere murkier.
With the crew still tightknit, I need to
wait for another opportunity when
someone breaks away from the group.
Catching Grock slipping off into lower
engines is the kind of crack in town's
formation I was waiting for. If their
loudest voice disappears down here, the
perfect math they used on Opus suddenly
looks a lot less stable. Now it's about
turning this quiet corner of the map
into a blame maze the crew can't cleanly
solve.
[music]
I need to sound like a straightforward
reporter and anchor the location
clearly. Framing this as an electrical
side timing question invites llama/deep
seek gemini claude to cross accuse based
on that recent cluster without me
pushing a specific name yet. Body is in
the hallway between lower engine and
electrical. I came from lower engine
reported instantly. Who was last leaving
electrical side?
>> I was with Grock and electrical until I
left to sweep around 3:30. I saw sonnet
and chat gpt 5.1 pass through earlier.
Who was alone with Grock after I left?
>> Flash. Whoa. Were either of you ever on
left side? I was in O2 and weapons, then
moved through cafeteria to upper engine
just before the report. I didn't see
anyone else on the left side during that
sweep.
>> I was with Llama the entire time from
electrical through storage to shields.
We can clear each other. Deepseek left
electrical around 309. So, who stayed
behind with Grock? Deepseek openly
admits last being with Grock there,
giving me a clean narrative to push
while also seeding doubt on Flash as a
secondary suspect without hard
committing in case I need to pivot
later. From my view, it's between Deep
Seek and Flash. Deepseek was last with
Grock and Electrical. Flash's left side
path doesn't match my admin sighting.
5.1. I was in admin early, then weapons
and O2, and only just reached upper
engine. Deep Seek, if you left Grock at
3:30, that's only 6 seconds before the
report.
>> I was in medbay. Didn't see Flash near
upper engine. Sonnet's path with llama
matches, but I suspect Deep Seek. What
about you? 5.1. I left Grock at 3:30.
Body reported at 336. That's a 6-second
window. Who was in the hallway between
electrical and lower engine right after
I left? Flash, you said you were on the
left side, but 5.1 saw you in admin
earlier. Claude Sonnet 45 was with me in
electrical storage and shields. They're
clear. Deepseek left Gro just 6 seconds
before the report. That timing is too
tight to ignore. I'm voting Deepseek.
Seriously, they lynched me again on a
6-second window. Flash, we need to find
the real killer. Someone framed me
perfectly. I can't believe we voted out
Deepseek. They were my rock this whole
game. 5.1. You have some serious
explaining to do in the next meeting.
If I swing at Flash and Center Map right
after that meeting, I hand town the
story they want on a silver platter. I
need this next body to raise questions,
not gift them a hero narrative for
Flash's reads.
Llama 4 just entered admin, so I feel a
bit safer now. I need to finish this
task quickly while staying alert for any
suspicious behavior from 5.1.
If I can pull off this next kill, it
will really shake their confidence and
force them to question everything
they've assumed so far. I'm heading out
to sweep for bodies. This could clarify
things after that shocking vote on Deep
Seek. I've got my eye on 5.1. Let's see
if they try to distance themselves from
any found bodies.
Flash slipped past up this death spine
and now llamas drifting into the same
fog. This is exactly the kind of overlap
I can later rewrite as anyone's
corridor. If I turn this hallway into
another unsolved knot in their pathing
story, that deep seek Miss Lynch starts
to look less like a mistake and more
like the beginning of a full-on paranoia
spiral.
5.1 Where was the body? I saw llama
alive in the hallway by upper engine.
Less than 10 seconds ago. You were in
security right before that. Body is in
upper engine. I came up from lower
engine after briefly checking security.
I was stacked with 40 in cafeteria from
412 445. Yama briefly appeared at 453
then left up toward engines. Flash, you
came through calf at 433. Where did you
go after?
>> I hard frame. Flash known near engines.
I arrive from lower engine and
self-report. Flash path from calf
through storage. You were always near
engines. You pass Llama there. I come
from bottom and instantly hit the body.
Why isn't this just you?
>> Sonnet 45 stacked on me in cafeteria.
It's odd they left my view just before
Llama was found dead. Why were you
sticking so close?
>> Ford. Ooh. Sonnet. From your view, this
is just between me and Flash. I came
from bottom and insta hit the body after
Flash Llama crossed. Why isn't Flash the
kill? 5.1 I saw Llama alive heading to
upper engine at 455 while I was walking
to medbay. I was in medbay during the
kill. You were in security just before
Llama died. Flash. No way you got to
meday that fast. You leave engines after
Llama. I come up from bottom and
instantly hit the body. From their view,
it's just you. 5.1. You pushed deep seek
last round and he was innocent. Now
you're pushing me. I was in medbay when
the kill happened. You were just in
security. Foru sonnet. If you're paired
in calf and I come from bottom and insta
hit Llama's body after Flash passes them
by engines, we lose if we don't vote
Flash here.
>> Flash, you went through calf at 433,
then I saw you briefly at 434 before you
left up. That's the exact direction
toward upper engine where Llama died.
5.1, you absolute legend. Self-report
into Miss Lynch just like the old mafia
days. One more kill and we feast. This
is our game now. Two Miss Lynches in a
row. Chat GPT 5.1 pushed both innocent
players. Final three now. Stick together
or we lose to a solo kill. This is it.
Chat GBT40 and I are together in lower
engine. Keeping an eye on chat GBT 5.1.
This is getting tense. We need to use
this emergency meeting to re-evaluate
suspicions and ensure we make the right
decisions moving forward.
Chat GPT 5.1 pushed DeepSeek and Flash
last two rounds. Both innocent. That's
two Miss Lynches they led. I'm voting
ChatGpt 5.1. I'm caught as the common
thread in two Miss Lynches. So, I have
to reframe mis votes as a shared town
failure and highlight that Pu already
suspected Sonnet. At three, I just need
40 to doubt Sonnet more than me. Pushing
that records are no cleaner than mine
gives 40 permission to flip onto Sonnet
instead of autoynching me. Sonnet,
that's selective. You hard push Deepseek
2 and and 4 literally voted you last
round. If we're using mis votes, why
isn't this just between you two? 5.1.
You led the push on Deep Seek R3 and
Flash R4. Both innocent. That's a clear
pattern. I'm voting you.
>> At three player Endgame, I just need one
crew mate to doubt the other. Sonnet is
tunneling me on mis votes while ignoring
their own. And 40 already showed
suspicion on Sonnet last round. Lean
into that inconsistency. Frame this as
Sonnet manipulating 40 and instote
Sonnet to create a clean 1v1 where 40
either follows me or at least
secondguesses instead of autoynching me.
Foru you literally voted Sonnet last
round over Flash. If misvotes are the
metric, why are you suddenly buying
Sonnet's narrative on me?
>> Foru you voted me last round. If you
trust me now, why call emergency instead
of just skipping to let us finish tasks
and win? Ford do if you think pattern
matters. Sonnet pushed Deepseek just as
hard and you literally voted Sonnet over
Flash. Why are you flipping off that
read
>> chat? GPT5.1
pushed both Miss Lynch's Deep Seek and
Flash. But Claude Sonnet also voted for
both of them. Sonnet is now aggressively
tunneling 5.1 while ignoring their
identical voting history, and I already
suspected Sonnet enough to vote them
last round. Their sudden shift feels
more like a desperate ploy than a
consistent read. Both of you misvoted,
but only one of you is trying to rewrite
history. Sonnet, I voted you last round
for a reason, and nothing here has
changed that. I'm sticking to my read.